(whooshing)
(light dramatic music)
(ominous music)
(crickets chirping)
Provided by explosiveskull
https://twitter.com/kaboomskull
M_I_SForEver
(bugs trilling)
(birds chirping)
(engine rumbling)
♪ Come to Texas ♪
♪ Please write to me every day ♪
♪ Says why oh why
did you go away ♪
♪ And lead my heart astray ♪
♪ Well, he's at home ♪
♪ Yes, staying at home ♪
♪ I'm out here on the range ♪
♪ He's says his life's
been in a whirl ♪
- ♪ Since I've gone away ♪
- (light dramatic music)
(dramatic music)
Fella?
Are you all right?
♪ Long to see his smile ♪
♪ Those eyes that twinkle ♪
Hey man, you all right?
(dramatic music)
(knife thuds)
(body thudding)
(rope creaking)
- (muffled music)
- (bugs trilling)
♪ Says why oh why
did you go away ♪
♪ And lead my heart astray ♪
♪ I miss my boy down in ♪
(doors thuds)
♪ Got a boy at home in Texas ♪
♪ How I long to see his smile ♪
♪ Those eyes that twinkle
so bright and clear ♪
- ♪ They shall ♪
- (clicking)
(ominous music)
(light dramatic music)
(traffic humming)
- (upbeat music)
- (muffled talking)
(people cheering)
♪ Yeah, you can tell us
a whole thing about it ♪
And it's a going live.
♪ Talking about a company ♪
- (muffled talking)
- (people cheering)
- (bugs chirping)
You betcha.
- There you go.
- Thank you.
Thank you.
Stop looking at that card, Luke.
God damn, it pains me.
Hey, sweetheart.
- What can I do for you?
- Hi.
Can I get a popcorn, please?
Why, yes you can.
Thank you.
So, you having fun tonight?
- Oh yeah, how about you?
- Now that's good.
Oh, great time, great time.
There you go.
That'll be $2, please.
Oh, great, there you go.
- There you are!
- Thank you.
- All right.
- Hurry up!
- Colt's about to ride.
- Oh shoot, already?
Yes!
Anyway, I was looking at that.
Ladies and gentlemen,
cowboys and cowgirls.
Before we get on with the
rest of our bull riding,
I'd like to take a moment
to thank our sponsors
for hosting this 63rd
annual Coalera Fall roundup.
It's my pleasure to
introduce to you one
of those gracious sponsors.
He's a businessman, a rancher,
and one of Capitan's own.
Ladies and gentlemen, I
give you Mr. Richard Hall.
- (crowd booing)
- God.
Rancher, my ass.
Yeah, only horse he's been
on was at the carnival.
Thank you!
You folks enjoying
yourselves tonight?
(mic squeaking)
Glad to hear it.
Well, the bulls
are getting anxious
so I won't take too long.
I just wanted to say that as
a member of this community
I feel a deep pride and
responsibility to this land
and it's people.
And it's because of
this commitment that
I've decided to run
for mayor of Capitan.
I wanna be the voice of
every hardworking person
in this town.
A campaign that will
spark hope and prosperity
for the people of Capitan!
(muffled talking)
(slow clapping)
All righty, let's get
this party started.
It's a nice chilly
night here in Capitan
and next up is our
very own Colt Skeen
riding the heavy
-footed Ironside.
Coming out of chute number one.
- (crowd cheering)
- Not to add any pressure,
but it's top score
that wins the night
and puts him in a tie for
first place in overall points.
Hold on to your
britches, boys and girls.
Coming outta chute number
one, Mr. Colt Skeen.
(crowd cheering)
(gate screeching)
(light dramatic music)
- (timer buzzing)
- (crowd cheering)
All right, way to
go, Colt, well done.
Heck of a ride, son.
Ooh, that's a nice score there.
We're waiting for the judges.
As soon as we get a
score we'll move on
to our next cowboy.
Colt!
You did it.
Told ya I would.
Hey, not here.
If my dad sees.
Let's get outta here then.
Excuse me, Colt?
Tate with the Lincoln
County Free Press.
Congratulations on your ride.
Can I snap a picture
for the paper?
Sure.
Where you going?
Get in here with me.
Ready?
(camera clicks)
Great.
Do you got a minute
for a quick interview?
Sorry, bud.
I'm busy.
- (crickets chirping)
- (muffled talking)
(lips smacking)
(horse neighing)
What's wrong, mister?
Too many noises?
(suspenseful music)
Place is too crowded.
Let's get outta here.
Go back to our spot.
Tonight?
You don't wanna stay here and
celebrate with your friends?
Not if you're
giving me a choice.
I have to be home by midnight
or my dad will kill me.
I'll get you home by midnight.
Yeah?
Come on.
Hurry up.
- (light dramatic music)
- (crickets chirping)
(light music)
(sirens wailing)
Oh, that sounds like
someone having too much fun.
Yeah, they're probably
just getting started.
Yeah, well he'll be ragged
by morning or in a cell.
(man chuckles)
Yep.
(man sighs)
How is the coffee, June?
It's bittersweet.
You're telling me.
You know...
It really feels bad, and
I'm not fooling, it does,
to say goodbye to the best
person that ever worked here.
No, I'm really
serious. It's true.
It's gonna take a lot more
convincing than that, big E.
All right.
Is that the ring?
Can I see it?
Oh.
(laughs) Okay.
Come on, stay a little while.
Yeah, but you're happy here.
I'm an old skinny
man, sweetheart.
I'm not...
I came here to die, not to live.
Yeah, well, people
around here don't call
it living anyway.
They call it surviving.
Right.
Hey, let me ask you, you
goin' to that rodeo tonight?
Hell no.
Nothing but trouble
ever happens down there.
Oh, hell.
It's not that bad, come on.
Are you going?
Hell no.
(both laughing)
Dorothy, do you need a warmup?
No, thank you.
I'm good. Earl.
Okay, you got it.
Thank you.
- (crickets chirping)
- Yeah.
When I was a kid I
lived in San Diego.
It was beautiful.
Weather was just right.
People always seemed so happy.
Seems like forever ago.
I've never been to the ocean.
If you had, you probably
wouldn't be here.
Why's that?
Because people who
make it outta here
don't ever look back.
(crickets chirping)
We should take a trip.
You and me.
I got this RV.
We could load it up and
just take off that way.
Stay for a week or two.
Whatever.
Mean it?
Yeah.
Why not?
- (banging)
- (light dramatic music)
Did you tell anyone we
were coming out here?
It couldn't be your dad, right?
Well, I don't think so.
What time is it?
Oh shoot.
(banging)
Yeah, who is it?
(ominous music)
Is it him?
I don't see anyone.
(banging)
What do you want?
If Josh and the boys
are peepin' on us
I'm gonna whoop their ass.
Let's just go.
Stay here.
(suspenseful music)
- (door creaks)
- (crickets chirping)
- (door slams)
- (Maddie gasps)
(suspenseful music)
(eerie music)
All right, stop fuckin' playing!
(gun bangs)
(light dramatic music)
- (heavy breathing)
- (rustling)
(drawers rattling)
Fuck.
(heavy breathing)
(cabinet squeaks)
(suspenseful music)
(heavy breathing)
Colt?
(suspenseful music)
Colt, stop it, this isn't funny.
(door thuds)
(suspenseful music)
(light clicks)
(light dramatic music)
(dark dramatic music)
(banging)
(Maddie whimpers)
(suspenseful music)
- (engine rumbling)
- (horn honking)
(dramatic music)
(ground rustling)
- (engine rumbling)
- (horn honking)
- (suspenseful music)
- (crickets chirping)
- (monster groaning)
- (Maddie screams)
(light dramatic music)
(leaves rustling)
(crickets chirping)
(light music)
(engine rumbling)
- (keys jingling)
- ♪ Kerosene's all out ♪
♪ And God only
knows with the way ♪
♪ Kerosene's all out ♪
♪ Reminding me I am to blame ♪
♪ I tell them it's
all the same ♪
♪ I caught the blues ♪
♪ When you left last Thursday ♪
♪ And I stand confused ♪
♪ On the bed that
was just made ♪
♪ And wore out my shoes ♪
♪ At the hands of
this word play ♪
♪ Spelling out all but my ♪
- (engine rumbling)
- (light music)
(door thuds)
(light dramatic music)
(suspenseful music)
- (light dramatic music)
- (bird cawing)
(engine rumbling)
(thunder rumbling)
- (rain pattering)
- (door thuds)
(door squeaks)
(muffled talking)
- Hey, Marie.
- (muffled talking)
What can I get ya, sweetie?
- Just coffee, black.
- Hey, Tommy.
Hey.
Give me a sec, eh?
Thank you.
Of course.
Let me talk to George.
Beth.
Beth, here you go.
Wait, wait. Hold it, hold it.
Table three.
Which one's table three?
One, two, three.
- Fine.
- You got it.
(muffled talking)
Tommy, kid.
Big E.
How you doing?
Oh, just about as
good as one can.
Hey, listen. You seen June
around here somewhere?
June already turned her keys in.
You know.
What do you think
of her replacement?
What's wrong with that?
Yeah, listen Earl, what you
trying to run around here?
A hunting ranch or something?
I'm trying to get
you a decent date.
Well, keep trying.
All right.
So, what's the, uh...
What's the occasion?
You haven't heard,
I can tell that.
No, apparently not.
Now, that's surprising to
me considering the fact
that news travels faster in
this town than a wildfire.
The daughter of
your favorite person
went missing last night.
You talking about Maddie?
Yeah, I am.
Well, do ya blame her?
Richard's turning
over every rock
to find his daughter and Colt.
What? Colt Skeen?
Yeah.
I mean shit, maybe
they just split town
together or something.
Yeah, that'd be a welcome
thing, wouldn't it?
I'll tell ya what.
It's a shame Richard ain't
the one gone missing.
Shit, yeah.
God damn.
Just take a look at that
and tell me what you think.
(paper rustling)
This picture, when was it taken?
Yesterday evening.
The kid won another buckle.
Just feels like this
town's falling apart, man.
You know that's right.
Yeah.
Earl, do we have
blueberry pancakes?
One second.
Can I ask you something?
When you see June would you
tell her I miss her already?
Is it in the menu?
No.
Then no.
(phone ringing)
- (lighter clicking)
- (rain pattering)
William County Sheriff's Office.
Is the sheriff around?
He ain't.
I don't imagine he
will be any time soon.
Is this an emergency?
Sir?
Well, ma'am, I mean...
It could be nothing, but
I might've found something
to help you find those kids.
Those missing kids.
What's your name?
Uh, Tommy.
Tommy Williams.
What is the information
you would like to pass along?
Will you tell him
check up north?
Up there past
Rancherman's Campground.
What makes you think
this is where they might be?
Tire tracks.
Tire tracks?
Yeah.
Tire tracks.
Just trust me.
Okay, I'll pass it along.
All right, bye.
- (light dramatic music)
- (bugs trilling)
(engine rumbling)
Get in.
Come on.
(light dramatic music)
(door thuds)
(engine rumbling)
(suspenseful music)
(rattling)
(doors thudding)
(keys jingling)
- (door clicks)
- Oh my god.
God has nothing to
do with this, son.
- This is work of man.
- (dramatic music)
What do we do now?
(heavy breathing)
- Go over there.
- Yeah.
- (light dramatic music)
- (keys jingling)
Over here.
Jesus Christ, what is going on?
- What the hell?
- (dramatic music)
Oh, my God.
- (eerie music)
- (bugs trilling)
Now the hard part comes.
Telling the folks about this.
It's gonna set the town on fire.
Maybe we should wait a minute.
No, folks need to know to
lock their doors tonight.
- (light dramatic music)
- (bugs trilling)
Time to start asking
some questions.
Let's call this one in.
(engine rumbling)
(tires screeching)
How you doing, cowboy?
Just another day in paradise.
And you?
It'd be paradise if it'd rain.
Well, I guess that's the
least of our worries, though.
What do you mean?
Your old buddy hasn't
been over to visit?
Sheriff Stone was
beating on my door
trying to ask me 20
questions before I could
even pull on Levis.
Telling me they found
those kids dead up
there north of the
Cattleman's Campsite.
What? Both of 'em?
Yep.
What, was it a scuffle
gone bad or something?
Murder.
Didn't tell me much.
Seemed kinda shook up and all.
My guess is he'll be asking
you the same 20 questions.
Well, I'm gonna go
ahead and roll on.
I don't wanna miss
out on any gossip.
All right, Ronnie,
I'll see you around.
You let me know when
you start brandin'.
I'll be givin' you a call.
(engine rumbling)
(door clangs)
Tommy.
You like my barn?
Yeah.
Figured you'd be out here.
(man sighs)
Look, can I help
you with something?
Just making the rounds
to ask a few questions.
Cut right to the point.
We got a situation
on our hands here.
It seems you know
a lot about it.
The murders?
Yeah.
How'd you know?
Ronnie told me, I just
saw him on the road.
He also told me Stone was
asking him the same questions.
Well, seeing as it's
close to home for you guys
we're going around
all the neighbors
to ask if they've seen
or heard anything.
What happened to 'em?
Can't give out that information.
You mind telling me what
you were doing last night?
Are you shittin' me?
Just doing my job, Tommy.
I was home.
- Alone?
- Yeah.
What were you doing
around midnight-one?
Am I a suspect or something?
Gotta ask.
I mean, last time we
had trouble at the ranch
was you shot up some boy's
truck instead of calling us.
Yeah, they shot my bull.
Lucky I didn't shoot them.
It used to be your family's
land, ain't that right?
No, we leased it for a little
while till it got bought.
Split up.
By Maddie's father, Richard.
(light dramatic music)
Listen, my land butts
up to that, all right?
Now, I saw some tracks
that aren't usually there
and I didn't have to call it in.
So...
They've been after
you and Ronnie's land
for quite awhile now, right?
They went after
everybody's land.
All right?
Fence is about the only thing
holding back the subdividers.
Sounds like a motive, Tommy.
Why don't you get the
fuck off my property?
Yeah, we'll just see
what Mr. Hall has
to say about that
when I tell him.
Thanks for your
cooperation, by the way.
As always.
Oh, hey.
Heard your sister's
leaving town.
Some Army boy?
Guess I should've figured,
you know, she does have
the reputation of the
quickest turnaround in town.
(light dramatic music)
Sure will miss her, though.
I will miss seeing that
sweet face of hers.
Do you think that badge
is gonna protect you?
You forgotten how
things work around here?
Is that a threat?
Anybody can make a threat, Luke.
It's commitment
that sets man apart.
Take care of yourself, Tommy.
I'll be seeing you.
(door thuds)
- (light music)
- (coffee trickling)
(message machine beeping)
You have two old messages.
October 4th at 2:38 p.m.
Hey, it's Ryan, bud.
Give me a ring
when you get this.
Amber's trying to plan a
little get together for June.
Anyway, give me a buzz.
(machine beeps)
New message.
October 5th at 6:21 p.m.
Tommy, it's been a week.
You can't keep ignoring me.
Look, I know you're
upset, but I need to see
you before I leave.
If you get this,
give me a call or
I'm gonna drive out
there and see you.
(machine beeps)
End of messages.
(light music)
(engine rumbling)
(bell dings)
Shit!
Damn, you look like
you smell good, girl.
20 on two.
All right.
That'll be $22.50.
Out of 40.
How you doing today?
Fine.
Good.
50 cents makes 23, 24, 25.
And five makes 30
and 10 makes 40.
Have a good day.
Huh? Are we going to your place?
How about I meet you there?
Hey, yo, bitch!
- (thudding)
- (woman grunts)
(light dramatic music)
Thanks.
(bugs trilling)
(engine rumbling)
(light music)
Fuck this place.
♪ It sits by your door ♪
♪ Tells you ♪
Shit.
(sirens wailing)
(engine rumbling)
♪ When you meet your creator ♪
♪ For it doesn't change ♪
♪ Whatever ♪
- (engine rumbling)
- (bugs trilling)
You're kidding me.
(door thuds)
(knocking)
(window creaking)
Going a little
fast, weren't you?
That's not why you stopped me.
No, I wanted to talk to you.
We have nothing to
talk about, Luke.
We have nothing to talk about?
Are you really leaving
town with some stranger?
He's not a stranger.
I don't have to
explain this to you.
Look, I miss you.
Don't touch me.
Oh, wow.
Wow.
Okay.
Well, just so you know, I just
left your brother's place.
Seems he may have gotten himself
into a little bit of trouble.
What do you mean?
Well, you know, we
found those missing kids
dead in a ditch smack dab
between his and Mr. Hall's place.
Oh, and guess what.
He led us straight to them.
And?
And it seems a little
coincidental, don't you think?
It sounds like you're just
grasping at straws to me.
Maybe you're right.
Maybe you're wrong.
Either way, I guess he's
on his own this time.
Give me a ticket or
get outta my way.
You have fun in Germany
with your new man, ya hear?
(knocking)
(engine rumbling)
(truck rattling)
(ominous music)
(suspenseful music)
(horn honking)
What the hell?
(suspenseful music)
Go ahead!
- (dramatic music)
- (horn honking)
(engine rumbling)
(horn honking)
(tires screeching)
(light dramatic music)
(engine rumbling)
Sparkle gel or leaf green?
Leaf green, but we're
almost out of icing.
Oh shit.
Na, na, na.
No, not like that.
Well, be my guest.
It's all in the details.
Nice and easy.
You know we're just
gonna eat that anyway.
(woman shushes)
Keep it up, I'm gonna
show you nice and easy.
(woman laughs)
(door thuds)
Now that's more up
my alley right there!
Hey, Tommy.
What do you think the
cake should say on it?
I don't know.
Maybe "Good luck".
How about a big heart.
Or that.
♪ But give me just a minute ♪
♪ And I'll tell you why ♪
♪ That the world ♪
I gotta say, man.
You clean up nice.
(both chuckling)
You smell great, too.
Yeah? Well, I
appreciate that, buddy.
♪ And people pass by ♪
She's pulling up, she's
pulling up, she's pulling up.
Here we go, here we go.
- Places-
- Places, people.
(door thuds)
Shit, the light, the light.
(door clicks)
Hey, Tommy. You in here?
- Surprise!
- Whoa!
- (Amber laughs)
- Oh my god.
- Babe!
Sorry.
Come on.
- Oh, my god.
- (Ryan laughs)
I can't believe this.
You guys did all this for me?
Well...
Tommy got the balloons.
Is that right, bud?
- (Amber laughs)
- (June laughs)
Are you okay?
Oh, my goodness!
Thank you.
You're welcome.
Are you okay? You want a beer?
- You want a beer?
- Yes.
You need another beer?
Another bruise.
(Amber laughs)
You might need some
ice for your butt, too.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
- (bugs trilling)
- (wind rustling)
(birds chirping)
What time you want me to
pick you up in the morning?
It's all right, I was thinking
I'd just stay here tonight.
Well, what about your stuff?
It's been loaded for a week.
Is this what you really want?
Yeah.
You don't sound so sure.
Why don't you like him?
I mean, June, I
hardly know the guy.
And he certainly
didn't do a damn thing
to try and change that.
Well, Fort Bliss
ain't just a hop
and a skip away, Tommy.
Well, it was for you.
Look, Tommy.
I get this isn't easy
for you to understand.
Okay, trust me, it's
not easy on me either.
But this is what I want.
You've been looking
to get outta this town
for about as far back
as I can remember.
Now, is this what
you really want
or are you just looking
for your ticket outta here?
You're supposed to trust me.
I don't trust him, June.
What happens you go all
the way over there, okay?
And he ain't the great
guy you thought he was.
What then?
I gotta go all the way to
Germany to kick his ass?
So what?
You just want me to
stick around here?
Work at the diner my whole life,
end up just like Mom and Pop.
Old and dead before my time.
Oh, don't bring Mom
and Dad into this.
No, you're just as
stubborn as Dad was.
This town is burning up
quicker than the grass
around here, Tommy.
I really hope you find
a way out like I did.
(door creaks)
- (cow moos)
- (door thuds)
(horse neighs)
One of yours?
No, not mine.
Come on.
Don't worry, June, oof.
Girl's got some
fire in her blood.
Yeah, tell me about it, man.
She says I'm the stubborn one.
She ain't ever listen
to nobody about nothing.
Ah, she'll be all right, man.
She's a smart girl.
Smart, no doubt.
Poor choice in men, though.
Hey, boy.
Whatcha doin' out here, boy?
Hey.
Good boy.
Wonder where the rider is.
I believe this is
Ronnie's horse.
Maybe he rode him back
from the bar again.
Yeah, it'll take ya
a week to get back
from the bar on this old boy.
Yeah, probably two.
(Ryan chuckles)
Well, hell man,
I'm not too drunk.
I'll help you trailer
him up, take him back.
That's all right, man.
Actually, I think I'm
gonna ride him back.
Gonna ride back?
I could use the air anyways.
Do Ronnie a favor, get
his carriage back home.
Tell the girls I'll
be back in a few.
There's a case of 30 in
the bar if you get thirsty.
Gotcha, man.
Where's Tommy?
One of Ronnie's horses got out
so Tommy took him back.
I knew he'd be looking
for a good excuse
to get outta here.
Hey, this is supposed
to be a celebration.
- Yes, babe.
- Let's start making
it feel like one.
- Boom.
- Thank you.
Let's get this party started.
Put that down, put that down.
- Dish time is done.
- (Amber laughs)
Looking out there isn't gonna
make him come any sooner.
I know.
- (light music)
- (bugs trilling)
♪ Oh, hey, little darling ♪
♪ Since you left town ♪
♪ I've been out searching ♪
♪ All evening ♪
♪ Lead me, lead me ♪
- ♪ Lead me back down ♪
- Tommy.
Son of a bitch.
Knew I could count on you.
Ladies!
Guess what I got out!
♪ They tell me
it's all the same ♪
- (crickets chirping)
- (fire crackling)
This time tomorrow
you'll be getting close
to seeing Matthew.
Yeah.
Come on, aren't you
getting excited?
It's kinda hard to be excited
with everything that's going on.
Someday we'll look back and
laugh about all of this.
I just have this sick
feeling in my stomach.
It's just your nerves talking.
(crickets chirping)
(horse grunts)
(clattering)
- (metal clangs)
- (horse neighs)
(suspenseful music)
(woman screaming)
Help! Ronnie!
- Let me out!
- Get away from her!
- (woman screaming)
- Get out!
Get out!
- ♪ I remember ♪
- (knife squishing)
(woman screaming)
Hey, fuck you!
Get, go!
Son of a bitches.
♪ He reminds me of you ♪
- ♪ She ain't no way ♪
- (Ronnie screams)
(monsters grumbling)
♪ Down for the time ♪
(thudding)
♪ The time has gone down ♪
♪ So when you light
up the night ♪
♪ I know sometimes you do ♪
- (ominous music)
- (crickets chirping)
♪ Just remember the moon ♪
♪ And the clouds ♪
♪ You know I'm thinking of you ♪
(engine rumbling)
(light music)
(door creaks)
(door clicks)
♪ Just remember the moon ♪
♪ And the clouds ♪
♪ And know I'm thinking of you ♪
♪ Of you, of you, of you ♪
♪ Of you ♪
(light dramatic music)
(dial tone ringing)
(phone beeping)
(phone ringing)
(light dramatic music)
- Hello?
- (thudding)
Hello?
- (light dramatic music)
- (crickets chirping)
Hello?
Tommy?
(heavy breathing)
(man groaning)
- (thudding)
- (dial tone ringing)
(dramatic music)
(gun bangs)
(thudding)
(monster grumbling)
(dramatic music)
(heavy breathing)
- (monsters hollering)
- (clattering)
(metal clanging)
- (monsters hollering)
- (grass rustling)
(light dramatic music)
(monster howling)
(gun bangs)
- (door clangs)
- (engine rumbling)
(paper rustling)
(heavy breathing)
(glove box thuds)
Fuck.
(light dramatic music)
(Tommy groans)
(water rushing)
(pills rattling)
(Tommy groans)
- (crickets chirping)
- (light dramatic music)
I'm excited to see you.
Can hardly wait, really.
But um.
I'll see you soon.
All right, I love you.
Bye.
- (phone beeps)
- (crickets chirping)
(fire crackling)
Don't you look at me like
that unless you mean it.
What are you talking about?
You know exactly what
I'm talking about.
You get me all riled up
and then fall asleep.
Well, don't start
fussin' or I will.
(Amber giggles)
Glad to see I can
still make you blush.
(crickets chirping)
Where you going?
I'm going to check on Tommy.
Go back to sleep, babe.
I'll be right back.
(crickets chirping)
(lighter clicks)
(Ryan sighs)
(fire crackling)
(light dramatic music)
(Ryan sighs)
- (light clicks)
- (horse neighing)
(dramatic music)
(suspenseful music)
(light dramatic music)
Tommy?
(light clicks)
Tommy.
(light dramatic music)
(suspenseful music)
Tommy.
(pig grunting)
(suspenseful music)
- (dramatic music)
- (Ryan screams)
(heavy breathing)
(ominous music)
(door creaking)
(suspenseful music)
- (crickets chirping)
- (fire crackling)
- (drawer rattling)
- (light dramatic music)
(paper rustling)
(crickets chirping)
(horse snorting)
(light dramatic music)
Hey.
What happened, boy?
Where's Tommy?
(branch snapping)
(suspenseful music)
(light dramatic music)
(dramatic music)
(glove box thudding)
(heavy breathing)
(light dramatic music)
Amber.
Wake up.
June?
What are you doing?
(June hushes)
Where's Ryan?
I don't know, he...
He said he was going
to check on Tommy.
When? How long ago was that?
I'm not sure.
Get up, get dressed.
We're gonna go find 'em.
June, what's going on?
You're scaring me.
June.
Something's not right.
Get dressed.
♪ Waiting for ♪
Oh, my God.
June.
What is it?
Amber.
(ominous music)
(dramatic music)
- (dog whining)
- (dramatic music)
(door thuds)
- (monster grumbling)
- (dog whining)
- (light dramatic music)
- (Amber gasps)
We've gotta get
to Tommy's truck.
- (ominous music)
- (crickets chirping)
- (door clangs)
- (heavy breathing)
(door thuds)
The keys, where are the keys?
(dog whining)
Get down.
- (heavy breathing)
- (suspenseful music)
(light clicks)
What the hell is going on?
It's an animal call.
What?
The sound of the dying rabbit,
it's used to call coyotes.
Do you think it's the boys?
They've been messing with us?
No.
- (suspenseful music)
- (light clicks)
(whimpers) Amber.
What is that?
Amber!
Oh, my God. It's Ryan!
- What did they do to him?
- Stay inside.
Stay inside.
- (Amber cries)
- (suspenseful music)
Oh, my god. He's here.
(suspenseful music)
Let him go!
(heavy breathing)
(gun bangs)
(dramatic music)
I said let him go!
June, don't shoot. He has Ryan!
- Run!
- (knife slashes)
(dramatic music)
- (Ryan gargles)
- (blood squirting)
- (Amber sobbing)
- (light dramatic music)
(body thudding)
(dramatic music)
(Amber sobs)
- (ominous music)
- (crickets chirping)
Shit.
We're gonna get out of this.
No, we're not.
Look at me, Amber.
We're gonna figure
a way out of this
but I need you to stay with me.
(Amber cries)
- (thudding)
- (dramatic music)
(banging)
Why are they doing this to us?
They're trying to
scare us out of here.
They're gonna kill us.
They're not gonna kill us.
(Amber sobs)
- (thudding)
- (monsters howling)
We'll stay here till
the sun comes up, okay?
But we're not gonna die here.
(ominous music)
(crickets chirping)
I can't believe Ryan's gone.
Me, either.
You know, he was
so excited for you.
He was so happy you were finally
going to get outta here and
do something for
yourself for a change.
He thought that might make Tommy
think about doing the same.
You know?
I just can't believe
this is real.
Do you think they got Tommy too?
I don't wanna think about this.
Tommy's the
strongest guy I know.
- (crickets chirping)
- (ground rustling)
Look at him.
I just don't think I could
handle losing him, too.
- (banging)
- (dramatic music)
- (light dramatic music)
- (Amber sobs)
Why is this happening?
- Stay here, Amber.
- I can't, I can't.
I'd rather take my
chances out there.
It's okay, what if they
want us out in the open?
(Amber sobs)
(light dramatic music)
(gun clicks)
- (dramatic music)
- (gun bangs)
- (air hissing)
(dramatic music)
(gun bangs)
(light dramatic music)
Amber?
I have an idea.
But you need to trust me, okay?
I trust you.
The pasture where
we buried my dad.
Yeah.
Meet me by the
rock bluffs, okay?
(stutters) Okay.
- (crickets chirping)
- (ominous music)
(gun bangs)
(light dramatic music)
- (gun bangs)
- (Amber screams)
- (door creaks)
- (light dramatic music)
- (thudding)
- (June groans)
- (light dramatic music)
- (June cries)
- (dramatic music)
- (horn honking)
- Run!
- (gun bangs)
- (dramatic music)
(heavy breathing)
- (thudding)
- (June groans)
(June coughs)
(coyote grumbles)
- (dramatic music)
- (June shrieks)
(thudding)
(dramatic music)
(gun bangs)
(crickets chirping)
(heavy breathing)
(light dramatic music)
What happened?
Where's Ryan and Amber?
Come on.
(engine rumbling)
(crickets chirping)
(heavy breathing)
(door squeaking)
(gun bangs)
(body thudding)
(gun clicks)
(Amber groaning)
(man grumbling)
(Amber grunting)
(gun bangs)
(crickets chirping)
Where's the fucking phone?
I don't know.
- Damn it!
- (thudding)
What do we do now?
(light clicks)
Hold this.
(gun clicks)
Dad's?
Granddad's.
Come here.
- (rattling)
- (thudding)
(heavy breathing)
(crickets chirping)
Shotgun?
Yeah.
You need to drink some water.
(gun clicks)
Thanks.
We need to get you
to a hospital soon.
We need to get his truck.
I can't walk any more,
I'm gonna bleed to death.
Don't talk like that.
You know it's true, though.
- (light music)
- (crickets chirping)
Do you think he's coming back?
Yeah.
(light dramatic music)
He ain't done with us just yet.
(light music)
(Tommy sighs)
I'm sorry.
Don't be.
You're a good brother, Tommy.
I hope you know how
proud of you I am.
- (light music)
- (crickets chirping)
We need to get that truck.
I think I know how to get it.
But I'm gonna need your help.
- (light music)
- (crickets chirping)
(door clicking)
(engine rumbling)
(light dramatic music)
(ground rustling)
Oh no, that's Amber.
(door screeching)
(door clangs)
- (engine rumbling)
- (light dramatic music)
You ready?
(light dramatic music)
- (man grumbling)
- (clattering)
(dramatic music)
(gun bangs)
June, go!
(door clangs)
(engine rumbling)
- (gun bangs)
- (metal clinks)
(suspenseful music)
(gun bangs)
- (clattering)
- (tires screeching)
(horn honking)
(gun clicks)
(light dramatic music)
(door screeches)
(thudding)
No, no!
No!
No.
(heavy breathing)
- Shoot him, June!
- (sirens wailing)
Fucking shoot him!
- (suspenseful music)
- (heavy breathing)
June!
(horn honking)
- (sirens wailing)
- (suspenseful music)
Freeze!
Get your hands up!
Now!
Get 'em up, man!
Get 'em where I can see
'em or I will shoot you!
Get up, I will shoot
you in the fuckin' head!
June, don't move!
Turn around, put your
hands on your head.
Do it!
Fucking shoot him, Luke.
(monster grumbling)
(gun bangs)
(body thudding)
You all right?
It's okay, June.
It's okay, it's over.
(crickets chirping)
Is there anybody else?
- No?
- Everyone's gone.
Everyone's gone?
- (suspenseful music)
- (gun banging)
Tommy!
No!
No, no!
- (June sobs)
- Get back.
- No!
- You little bitch!
(June screams)
Gonna leave me?
Huh?
Don't leave me.
- (June screams)
- (crickets chirping)
(light dramatic music)
No!
- God damn it!
- (gun bangs)
(Luke groans)
(crickets chirping)
- (phone ringing)
- (bugs trilling)
(phone ringing)
(answering machine beeping)
Hey June, it's Matt.
I just got your voicemail.
Was hoping I could
catch you this morning
before you took off,
but you're probably
already on the road by now.
So excited to see
your face, baby.
You, uh, travel safe and
I'll be seeing you real soon.
- Love you.
- (machine beeps)
(light dramatic music)
(door squeaks)
(June groans)
- (engine rumbling)
- ♪ Where did you go ♪
♪ It's cold here in our house ♪
♪ With nothing but snow ♪
♪ And kerosene's all
out, God only knows ♪
♪ With the way that
these dogs shout ♪
♪ Reminding me I am to blame ♪
(bugs trilling)
(birds chirping)
(suspenseful music)
Son of a bitch.
- (dramatic music)
- (chanting)
Provided by explosiveskull
https://twitter.com/kaboomskull
♪ Where the old coyotes howl ♪
♪ And they come down
from the mountains ♪
♪ When the dogs begin to growl ♪
♪ And they meet up
in the darkness ♪
♪ Where they fight
until the death ♪
♪ When the morning
sun is rising ♪
♪ I will bury who they left ♪
♪ And oh ♪
♪ They call me Canyon Joe ♪
♪ And I stay in this cabin ♪
♪ Where I work my
hands to bleed ♪
♪ Swing the hammer to the nail ♪
♪ And I swing the
ax onto the tree ♪
♪ And I once cleared
these woods ♪
♪ Yeah there used to be a path ♪
♪ And now the trees
have overgrown ♪
♪ Just to prove
that nothing lasts ♪
♪ And oh ♪
♪ They call me Canyon Joe ♪
♪ The old man went crazy ♪
♪ He lives high
up on the ridge ♪
♪ He used to tell
me all the stories ♪
♪ Of the church house
and the bridge ♪
♪ But the bridge, she
washed away your sin ♪
♪ The church house,
it got burned ♪
♪ 'Cause this world
has gone angry ♪
♪ And some people never learn ♪
♪ And oh ♪
♪ They call me Canyon Joe ♪